Register of the Rodney Kennedy-Minott Papers, 1967-1994
Hoover Institution Archives
- Ambassador to Sweden office file, 1977-1980
  - 1979
    - Correspondence
      - Hedin, Sven Fr., Ambassador (Box-folder 13: 72)
      - Hellstrom, Nils, Mr. (Box-folder 13: 73)
      - Hernod, Torsten, Mr. (Box-folder 13: 74)
      - Hernelius, Allan, Mr. (Box-folder 13: 75)
      - Hesburgh, Theodore M., Father (memorandum enclosed) (Box-folder 13: 76)
      - Hill, Brian Clarence, Ambassador (Box-folder 13: 77)
      - Hillys, Joe, Mr. (Box-folder 13: 78)
      - Hinton, Dean E., Ambassador and Mrs. (Box-folder 13: 79)
      - Hishongua, Mr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 13: 80)
      - Hogberg, Hillevi, Ms. (Box-folder 13: 81)
      - Hokby, Bertil, Mr. (Box-folder 13: 82)
      - Holmback, Barbro, Ms. (Box-folder 13: 83)
      - Holmberg, Eke, Prof. (Box-folder 13: 84)
      - Hopkins, Henry T., Mr. (Box-folder 13: 85)
      - Houghteling, Joseph C., Mr. (Box-folder 13: 86)
      - Hoyt, Mary, Ms. (Box-folder 13: 87)
      - Hunter, Robert E., Esquire (Box-folder 13: 88)
      - Hurtig, Sylvia, Mrs. (program is included) (Box-folder 13: 89)
      - Huyser, Robert E. (Box-folder 13: 90)
      - Ilamsson, Per, Mr. (Box-folder 13: 91)
      - Ingalls, Walter M. (Box-folder 13: 92)
      - Isaacs, Maxine, Ms. (Box-folder 13: 93)
      - Jenkins, Thomas M. (Box-folder 14: 1)
      - Johansson, Bengt K.A., Mr. (Box-folder 14: 2)
      - Johansson, Bengt Vilgot (Box-folder 14: 3)
      - Johnson, Dan, Mr. (Box-folder 14: 4)
      - Johnson, James A., Mr. (Box-folder 14: 5)
      - Jonsson, Hans-Eke (telegram is enclosed) (Box-folder 14: 6)
      - Jonsson, Kerstin, Ms. (Box-folder 14: 7)
      - Jordan, Hamilton, Esquire (Box-folder 14: 8)
      - Jordan, Nancy, Ms. (Box-folder 14: 9)
      - Jorler, Gun, Ms. (Box-folder 14: 10)
      - Karlernas, Ingvar (Box-folder 14: 11)
      - Karnekull, Timo (Box-folder 14: 12)
      - Katz, Sherman E., Mr. (Box-folder 14: 13)
      - Kaufman, Joanne, Ms. (Box-folder 14: 14)
      - Keating, Michael R., Colonel (Box-folder 14: 15)
      - Kirkely, Paula, Ms. (Box-folder 14: 16)
      - Klackenberg, Lennart, Mr. (Box-folder 14: 17)
      - Klintstam, Mr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 14: 18)
      - Koblik, Steven, Prof. (Box-folder 14: 19)
      - Koch, Erland von, Prof. (Box-folder 14: 20)
      - Kraft, Tim, Mr. (Box-folder 14: 21)
      - Kronmark, Eric, Honorable (Box-folder 14: 22)
      - Kuniyuki, Yukio A., Mr. (Box-folder 14: 23)
      - Lampus, Helen M., Ms. (Box-folder 14: 24)
      - Lander, Don, Mr. (Box-folder 14: 25)
      - Lapinsky, M.J., Mr. (Box-folder 14: 26)
      - La Roche, Richard, Mr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 14: 27)
      - Larsson, Allan, Mr.(letter in Swedish is enclosed) (Box-folder 14: 28)
      - Larsson, Arne, Mr., Mayor (Box-folder 14: 29)
      - Larsson, Janerik, Mr. (Box-folder 14: 30)
      - Leidel, Donald C., Esquire (Box-folder 14: 31)
      - Leifland, Leif, Honorable (Box-folder 14: 32)
      - Lepape, Jeffrey, Mr. (handwritten notes by Rodney Kennedy-Minott and a telegram are enclosed) (Box-folder 14: 33)
      - Lerner, Louis A., Honorable (Box-folder 14: 34)
      - Levy, Hans W., Mr. (Box-folder 14: 35)
      - Lewis, Tara (Box-folder 14: 36)
      - Lilliecreutz, Bengt, Mr. (Box-folder 14: 37)
      - Lindh, Pia, Ms. (Box-folder 14: 38)
      - Ling, David, Mr. (Box-folder 14: 39)
      - Lipshutz, Robert, Esquire (Box-folder 14: 40)
      - Littlefield, E.W., Mr. (Box-folder 14: 41)
      - Lodato, Dominic J., J.S.C. (Box-folder 14: 42)
      - Lundborg, Agnes Lagerquist, Mrs. (Box-folder 14: 43)
      - Lurton, Andre, Mr. (Box-folder 14: 44)
      - Marks, William, Mr. (Box-folder 14: 45)
      - Marnell, Gunnar, Mr. (Box-folder 14: 46)
      - Mattsson, Mabel, Mrs. (Box-folder 14: 47)
      - McIlwain, Samuel D., Esquire (Box-folder 14: 48)
      - Meany, George, Mr. (Box-folder 14: 49)
      - Meinen, Kenneth L., Mr. (Box-folder 14: 50)
      - Melkersson, Marianne, Dr. (Box-folder 14: 51)
      - Mercurio, Michael J. (Box-folder 14: 52)
      - Miller, Paul M., Mr. (Box-folder 14: 53)
      - Miller, Penny, Ms. (Box-folder 14: 54)
      - Minott, Joseph A., Mr. (Box-folder 14: 55)
      - Moe, John, Mr. (Box-folder 14: 56)
      - Moe, Richard (Box-folder 14: 57)
      - Molin, Rune, Mr. (Box-folder 14: 58)
      - Moller, Gosta, Mr. (Box-folder 14: 59)
      - Mondale, Walter F., Honorable (Box-folder 14: 60)
      - Moose, Richard M., Esquire (Box-folder 14: 61)
      - Morley, Roger H. (Box-folder 14: 62)
      - Morrow, David L., Mr. (Box-folder 14: 63)
      - Moynihan, Daniel P., Honorable (Box-folder 14: 64)
      - Munkberg, Carl-Olov, Mr. (Box-folder 14: 65)
      - Murphy, Tom, Mr. (Box-folder 14: 66)
      - Murray, D. Michael, Mr. (Box-folder 14: 67)
      - Myrdal, Alva (Box-folder 14: 68)
      - Niblaeus, Kerstin, Ms. (Box-folder 14: 69)
      - Nilsson, A. (Box-folder 14: 70)
      - Nilsson, Lars-Ake, Mr. (Box-folder 14: 71)
      - Nilsson, Sam, Dr. (typescript copy of a report is enclosed) (Box-folder 14: 72)
      - Nordenfalk, Johan (Box-folder 14: 73)
      - Nordin, Magnus, Mr. (Box-folder 14: 74)
      - Novelli, Michael Peter, Mr.(handwritten notes are enclosed) (Box-folder 14: 75)
      - Nygren, Jan, Mr. (Box-folder 14: 76)
      - Nystrom, Agneta, Mrs. (Box-folder 14: 77)
      - O'Connor, John J., Bishop (Box-folder 14: 78)
      - Ohlin, Bertil, Mrs. (Box-folder 14: 79)
      - Olander, Jan (Box-folder 14: 80)
      - Olsson, Einar, Mr. (Box-folder 14: 81)
      - Ordforanden, LO (Box-folder 14: 82)
      - Orjes, Rolf, Mr. (Box-folder 14: 83)
      - Ottinger, Richard L., and Mrs.(handwritten letter is enclosed) (Box-folder 14: 84)
      - Owens, John P. (Box-folder 14: 85)
      - Oyler, Soldanella, Ms. (Box-folder 14: 86)
      - Padgett, Dorothy, Ms. (Box-folder 14: 87)
      - Pehlsson, Nils Iwar, Messers. (Box-folder 14: 88)
      - Palme, Olof, Mr. (Box-folder 14: 89)
      - Palme, Rutger, Mr. (Box-folder 14: 90)
      - Pelsson, Roland, Mr. (Box-folder 14: 91)
      - Parrish, Frances, Ms. (Box-folder 14: 92)
      - Paulsson, Eva (Box-folder 14: 93)
      - Pearson, Pamela, Ms. (Box-folder 14: 94)
      - Peetz, John E., Mr. (Box-folder 14: 95)
      - Pell, Claiborne, Honorable (Box-folder 14: 96)
      - Percy, Charles H. (Box-folder 14: 97)
      - Perry, Jack, Esquire (Box-folder 14: 98)
      - Petersen, Jeffrey, His Excellency, Sir (Box-folder 14: 99)
      - Phillips, Michael, Mr. (Box-folder 14: 100)
      - Pickering, Thomas R., Honorable (Box-folder 15: 1)
      - Pilo, Nils, Mr. (Box-folder 15: 2)
      - Plante, David (handwritten) (Box-folder 15: 3)
      - Platen, Gustav von, Mr. (Box-folder 15: 4)
      - Rainwater, Betty, Ms. (Box-folder 15: 5)
      - Ramel, Stig, Mr. (Box-folder 15: 6)
      - Rasmussen, Waldo (Box-folder 15: 7)
      - Read, Ben, Esquire (Box-folder 15: 8)
      - Reed, Richard R., Jr. (Box-folder 15: 9)
      - Reland, Stina, Ms. (Box-folder 15: 10)
      - Rentschler, James M., Mr. (Box-folder 15: 11)
      - Riccio, Robert A., Mr. (letter and schedule in Swedish are enclosed) (Box-folder 15: 12)
      - Ridway, Rozanne L., Honorable (Box-folder 15: 13)
      - Rockefeller, David, Mr. (Box-folder 15: 14)
      - Roos, Bjorn-Erik, Prof. (Box-folder 15: 15)
      - Rosberg, Gorn (Box-folder 15: 16)
      - Rubenowitz, Ewerth, Mr. (Box-folder 15: 17)
      - Russo, Marty, Honorable (Box-folder 15: 18)
      - Sandler, Eke, Prof. (printed copy is enclosed) (Box-folder 15: 19)
      - Saunders, Lawrence M., Mr. (Box-folder 15: 20)
      - Sawetamal, Suban, His Excellency (Box-folder 15: 21)
      - Schaefer, Philip A. and Judy (Box-folder 15: 22)
      - Schneible, Douglas S., Mr. (telegrams are enclosed) (Box-folder 15: 23)
      - Schriver, Dorothy, Ms. (Box-folder 15: 24)
      - Schultz, Theodore W., Prof. (Box-folder 15: 25)
      - Seaborg, Glenn T., Dr. (leaflet is enclosed) (Box-folder 15: 26)
      - Seeberg, Marta, Ms. (Box-folder 15: 27)
      - Sellin, Theodore, Mr. (Box-folder 15: 28)
      - Sherlock, Allan A., Mrs. (Box-folder 15: 29)
      - Sherwood, Bob (Box-folder 15: 30)
      - Shroyer, Lawrence E., Mr (Box-folder 15: 31)
      - Shulman, Marshall, Esquire (Box-folder 15: 32)
      - Sinclair, Henry B., Mr. (Box-folder 15: 33)
      - Singer, Isaac and Alma (Box-folder 15: 34)
      - Skog, Katharine M. A., Mrs. (Box-folder 15: 35)
      - Slater, J.E., Mr. (Box-folder 15: 36)
      - Slurff, Frank, Mr. (Box-folder 15: 37)
      - Smith, Frederick, Jr., Mr. (Box-folder 15: 38)
      - Smith, Lowell V., Honorable, Mayor (Box-folder 15: 39)
      - Smith, Michael J., Mr. (Box-folder 15: 40)
      - Soedewo, Eri, His Excellency, Ambassador (Box-folder 15: 41)
      - Soffe, David E., Mr. (Box-folder 15: 42)
      - Sohns, Ernest, Dr. (Box-folder 15: 43)
      - Spengberg, Fru Elly (handwritten notes by Rodney Kennedy-Minott are enclosed) (Box-folder 15: 44)
      - Spitzer, Jack J. (Box-folder 15: 45)
      - Springsteen, George S. (Box-folder 15: 46)
      - Stadtler, Walter E., Mr. (Box-folder 15: 47)
      - Stenman, Kenneth C., Rev. (Box-folder 15: 48)
      - Stern, Isaac, Mr. (memorandum is enclosed) (Box-folder 15: 49)
      - Stewart, Cyrus S., Dr. (Box-folder 15: 50)
      - Strandmark, Katarina, Ms. (Box-folder 15: 51)
      - Strate, Bengt, Mr. (Box-folder 15: 52)
      - Strauss, Harlan J., Dr. (Box-folder 15: 53)
      - Stromstedt, Bo, Mr. (Box-folder 15: 54)
      - Sundberg, Ingrid, Ms. (Box-folder 15: 55)
      - Sutherland, V.L., Mr. (Box-folder 15: 56)
      - Svedin, Goran, Mr. (Box-folder 15: 57)
      - Switzer, Walter E., Mr. (Box-folder 15: 58)
      - Sydow, Kristian von, Mr. (Box-folder 15: 59)
      - Tams, James R., Mrs. (Box-folder 15: 60)
      - Taubel, B. (Box-folder 15: 61)
      - Thedin, Nils (Box-folder 15: 62)
      - Tell, Bjorn, Mr. (Box-folder 15: 63)
      - Thomas, Joseph, His Excellency (Box-folder 15: 64)
      - Thompson, Llewellyn, Mrs. (Box-folder 15: 65)
      - Torstensson, Torsten, Mr. (Box-folder 15: 66)
      - Tromald, John P., Dr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 15: 67)
      - Tuma, Jan, Mr. (Box-folder 15: 68)
      - Turkin, Marshall W., Mr. (Box-folder 15: 69)
      - Turner, Betty Wade, Ms. (Box-folder 15: 70)
      - Tysk, Erik, Mr. (Box-folder 15: 71)
      - Ullsten, Ola, Honorable (Box-folder 15: 72)
      - University of Southern California (Box-folder 15: 73)
      - Van Deerlin, Lionel, Honorable (Box-folder 15: 74)
      - Vance, Cyrus R., Honorable (Box-folder 15: 75)
      - Vest, George S. (Box-folder 15: 76)
      - Vindeveg, Leif, Mr. (Box-folder 15: 77)
      - Vine, Richard D., Esquire (Box-folder 15: 78)
      - Waldron, M.D.P., His Excellency (Box-folder 15: 79)
      - Wallenberg, Marcus, Mr. (Box-folder 15: 80)
      - Warnke, Paul, Esquire (Box-folder 15: 81)
      - Weinberg, Steven, Prof. (Box-folder 15: 82)
      - Weldon, Garth, Mr. (Box-folder 15: 83)
      - Wennerberg, Vibeke, Mr. (Box-folder 15: 84)
      - Westerberg, Lasse, Mr. (Box-folder 15: 85)
      - Wiberg, Ingrid Segerstedt, Ms. (Box-folder 15: 86)
      - Widen, Albin, Mr. (Box-folder 15: 87)
      - Wikstrom, Jan-Erik, Mr. (Box-folder 15: 88)
      - Williams, Samuel L., Honorable (Box-folder 15: 89)
      - Williams, Tony (Box-folder 15: 90)
      - Wilmink, Janet M. (handwritten notes by Rodney Kennedy-Minott are enclosed) (Box-folder 15: 91)
      - Wise, Phil, Esquire (Box-folder 15: 92)
      - Wolff, Alan, Mr. (Box-folder 15: 93)
      - Woods, Ronald, Mr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 15: 94)
      - Wyatt, David, Esquire (Box-folder 15: 95)
      - Yoon, Ha Jong, His Excellency, Ambassador (Box-folder 15: 96)
      - Young, Andrew, Honorable (Box-folder 15: 97)
    - Memoranda
      - January (Box-folder 16: 1)
      - February (Box-folder 16: 2)
      - March (Box-folder 16: 3)
      - April (Box-folder 16: 4)
      - May (Box-folder 16: 5)
      - June (Box-folder 16: 6)
      - July (Box-folder 16: 7)
      - August (Box-folder 16: 8)
      - September (Box-folder 16: 9)
      - October (Box-folder 16: 10)
      - November (Box-folder 16: 11)
      - December (Box-folder 16: 12)
    - Schedules
      - January (Box-folder 16: 13)
      - February (Box-folder 16: 14)
      - March (Box-folder 16: 15)
      - April (Box-folder 16: 16)
      - May (Box-folder 16: 17)
      - June (Box-folder 16: 18)
      - July (Box-folder 16: 19)
      - August (Box-folder 17: 1)
      - September (Box-folder 17: 2)
      - October (Box-folder 17: 3)
      - November (Box-folder 17: 4)
      - December (Box-folder 17: 5)
    - Newsletters (Box-folder 17: 6)
    - Notes (handwritten) (Box-folder 17: 7)
    - Telegrams
      - January (Box-folder 17: 8)
      - February (Box-folder 17: 9)
      - March (Box-folder 17: 10)
      - April (Box-folder 17: 11)
      - May (Box-folder 17: 12)
      - June (Box-folder 17: 13)
      - July (Box-folder 17: 14)
      - August (Box-folder 17: 15)
      - September (Box-folder 17: 16)
      - October (Box-folder 17: 17)
      - November (Box-folder 17: 18)
      - December (Box-folder 17: 19)
    - Printed matter (magazine is enclosed) (Box-folder 17: 20)
    - Clippings (Box-folder 17: 21)
  - 1980
    - Correspondence
      - Unidentified (Box-folder 18: 1)
      - General (Box-folder 18: 2)
      - Aaron, David, Mr. (Box-folder 18: 3)
      - Abramowitz, Morton I., Honorable (Box-folder 18: 4)
      - Addabbo, Joseph P., Honorable, M.C. (Box-folder 18: 5)
      - Agede, Abate, Honorable (Box-folder 18: 6)
      - Alexander, N.P., Honorable (Box-folder 18: 7)
      - Allen, James R., General (Box-folder 18: 8)
      - Almqvist, Jackie G., Ms. (handwritten draft of a letter by Rodney Kennedy-Minott is enclosed) (Box-folder 18: 9)
      - Anderson, Hunk (Box-folder 18: 10)
      - Andersson, Ege, Mr. (Box-folder 18: 11)
      - Andersson, Sten, Mr. (Box-folder 18: 12)
      - Andrews, Mary (Box-folder 18: 13)
      - Atkinson, A.W., Maj. Gen. (Box-folder 18: 14)
      - Barnaby, Frank, Dr. (Box-folder 18: 15)
      - Barnes, Harry G., Jr. (Box-folder 18: 16)
      - Beard, Tom, Mr. (Box-folder 18: 17)
      - Bellmon, Henry, Honorable (Box-folder 18: 18)
      - Bender, Andrea, Ms. (Box-folder 18: 19)
      - Benedick, Richard E., Ambassador (Box-folder 18: 20)
      - Bergquist, George W. (handwritten notes are included) (Box-folder 18: 21)
      - Blum, Barbara, Ms. (Box-folder 18: 22)
      - Blumenberg, Ulf, Mr. (Box-folder 18: 23)
      - Bolton, Richard A. (Box-folder 18: 24)
      - Bray, Charles W. III, Mr. (Box-folder 18: 25)
      - Brement, Marshall, Mr. (Box-folder 18: 26)
      - California State University, Hayward (Box-folder 18: 27)
      - Canada College, California (Box-folder 18: 28)
      - Canney, Paul, Mr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 18: 29)
      - Carlucci, Frank, Ambassador (Box-folder 18: 30)
      - Carter, Jimmy, Mrs. (Box-folder 18: 31)
      - Cederstrom, Yvonne, Ms. (Box-folder 18: 32)
      - Charwick, Anthony C., Mr. (Box-folder 18: 33)
      - Childs, Marquis, Mr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 18: 34)
      - Church, Frank, Honorable (Box-folder 18: 35)
      - City College of San Francisco, California (Box-folder 18: 36)
      - Clark, Navy K., Mr. (Box-folder 18: 37)
      - Cohen, Edward M. (Box-folder 18: 38)
      - College of San Mateo, California (Box-folder 18: 39)
      - Conger, Clement, Mr. (brochure is enclosed) (Box-folder 18: 40)
      - Connors, Eleanor, Ms. (Box-folder 18: 41)
      - Cormack, Allan (handwritten) (Box-folder 18: 42)
      - Coughlan, Robert, Mr. (Box-folder 18: 43)
      - Cranston, Alan, Honorable (Box-folder 18: 44)
      - Crawley, Paul K., Col. and Mrs., USA (Box-folder 18: 45)
      - Dean, Robert D., Mr. (Box-folder 18: 46)
      - Donaldson, Paul, Mr. (Box-folder 18: 47)
      - Drachkovitch, Milorad M. (Box-folder 18: 48)
      - Drndic, Ljubomir, His Excellency, Ambassador (Box-folder 18: 49)
      - Duberman, David, Mr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 18: 50)
      - Duignan, Peter, Dr. (Box-folder 18: 51)
      - Ek, Simone, Ms. (Box-folder 18: 52)
      - Elderkin, Lannie, Ms. (Box-folder 18: 53)
      - Eliasson, Jan, Mr. (Box-folder 18: 54)
      - Feinstein, Dianne, Honorable (Box-folder 18: 55)
      - Funseth, Robert L., Esquire (Box-folder 18: 56)
      - Golden, John, Lt. Col., USAF (Box-folder 18: 57)
      - Goldfield, David R., Prof. (Box-folder 18: 58)
      - Gomperts, Robert, Mr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 18: 59)
      - Goodby, James E., Honorable (Box-folder 18: 60)
      - Granum, Rex, Mr. (Box-folder 18: 61)
      - Griffin, Ruth J., Mrs. (Box-folder 18: 62)
      - Gushaw, Evangelina (Box-folder 18: 63)
      - Hagrup, Knut, Dr. (Box-folder 18: 64)
      - Hallin, Anders, Mr. (Box-folder 18: 65)
      - Hambraeus, Gunnar, Prof. (Box-folder 18: 66)
      - Hamilton, Lee, Honorable (Box-folder 18: 67)
      - Hamrin, Jeannie M., Dr. (Box-folder 18: 68)
      - Hansson, Hans, Honorable (Box-folder 18: 69)
      - Harmon, William R., Mr. (Box-folder 18: 70)
      - Harpole, Mark, Mr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 18: 71)
      - Hart, John A., Mr. (Box-folder 18: 72)
      - Hassett, Frederick H. (Box-folder 18: 73)
      - Hay-Adams Hotel, Washington, D.C. (Box-folder 18: 74)
      - Hernelius, Allan, Mr. (Box-folder 18: 75)
      - Hidalgo, Edward, Honorable (Box-folder 18: 76)
      - Hinkley, Gerald M. (Box-folder 18: 77)
      - Hinton, Deane R., Honorable (Box-folder 18: 78)
      - Hirdman, Sven, Mr. (Box-folder 18: 79)
      - Howard, Frances Humphrey (Box-folder 18: 80)
      - Huth, Vanja, Mrs. (Box-folder 18: 81)
      - Jamieson, Kelly A., Miss (Box-folder 18: 82)
      - Johnson, Jim, Mr. (Box-folder 18: 83)
      - Johnston, Douglas M., Mr. (Box-folder 18: 84)
      - Jordan, Hamilton, Esquire (Box-folder 18: 85)
      - Jordan, Nancy, Ms. (Box-folder 18: 86)
      - Kang, Yung Kyoo, Honorable (Box-folder 18: 87)
      - Karlstrom, Signe, Mrs. (Box-folder 18: 88)
      - Katz, Sherman E. (printed matter is enclosed) (Box-folder 18: 89)
      - Kinntorph, Boo, Mr. (Box-folder 18: 90)
      - Kirkland, Lane, Mr. (Box-folder 18: 91)
      - Klutznick, Philip M., Honorable (Box-folder 18: 92)
      - Kraft, Tim, Mr. (Box-folder 18: 93)
      - Kristensson, Astrid, Ms. (Box-folder 18: 94)
      - Krepp, E., Honorable (Box-folder 18: 95)
      - Leff, Martin J., Mr. (Box-folder 18: 96)
      - Leifland, Leif, Mr. (Box-folder 18: 97)
      - Levy, Lawrence, Mr. (Box-folder 18: 98)
      - Linday, Mats, Mr. (Box-folder 18: 99)
      - Linder, Jorgen, Mr. (Box-folder 18: 100)
      - Lindkvist, Margareta, Ms. (Box-folder 18: 101)
      - Litzell, Catharina (Box-folder 18: 102)
      - Lyman, Richard W., Ph.D. (Box-folder 18: 103)
      - Malek, P. (handwritten) (Box-folder 19: 1)
      - Manfred, Ernest F., Mr. (Box-folder 19: 2)
      - Mensson, Yngve R., Mr. (Box-folder 19: 3)
      - Marks, William, Mr. (Box-folder 19: 4)
      - Mayer, James E., Mr. (Box-folder 19: 5)
      - McCloskey, Paul N., Jr., Honorable (Box-folder 19: 6)
      - McCune, Ellis E. (Box-folder 19: 7)
      - McGiffert, David E., Honorable (Box-folder 19: 8)
      - McIlwain, Samuel D., Mr. (Box-folder 19: 9)
      - Menafee, R.L., Mr. (Box-folder 19: 10)
      - Mercurio, Michael J. (Box-folder 19: 11)
      - Miles, John, Mr. (Box-folder 19: 12)
      - Miller, Penny, Ms. (Box-folder 19: 13)
      - Miller, William F., Dr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 19: 14)
      - Mineta, Norman Y., Honorable (Box-folder 19: 15)
      - Minott, Joseph A., Mr. (Box-folder 19: 16)
      - Moe, Dick, Mr. (Box-folder 19: 17)
      - Mondale, Walter F., Honorable (Box-folder 19: 18)
      - Montouri, Gary W., and Mrs. (Box-folder 19: 19)
      - Moore, Stephen, Mr. (Box-folder 19: 20)
      - Morad, James, Mr. (Box-folder 19: 21)
      - Mosse, George F., Mr. (Box-folder 19: 22)
      - Murray, D. Michael, Mr. (Box-folder 19: 23)
      - Muskie, Edmund S., Honorable (Box-folder 19: 24)
      - Myrdal, Alva, Mrs. (Box-folder 19: 25)
      - Neal, Richard C., Mr. (Box-folder 19: 26)
      - Nelson, David, Mr. (Box-folder 19: 27)
      - Newsom, David D., Honorable (Box-folder 19: 28)
      - Nilsson, Sam, Mr. (Box-folder 19: 29)
      - Nilsson, Lars-Eke, Mr. (Box-folder 19: 30)
      - Nimitz, Matthew, Honorable (Box-folder 19: 31)
      - Nygren, Jan, Mr. (Box-folder 19: 32)
      - Oberstar, James L., Honorable (Box-folder 19: 33)
      - Owens, John, Mr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 19: 34)
      - Padgett, Dorothy, Ms. (leaflet is enclosed) (Box-folder 19: 35)
      - Panetta, Leon E., Honorable (Box-folder 19: 36)
      - Pell, Claiborne, Honorable (Box-folder 19: 37)
      - Pellegrino, Lewis, Sr., Mr. (Box-folder 19: 38)
      - Pernow, Bengt, Prof. (Box-folder 19: 39)
      - Perry, Jack R., Honorable (Box-folder 19: 40)
      - Petzen, Hans, Mr. (Box-folder 19: 41)
      - Pickering, Thomas R. (Box-folder 19: 42)
      - Plym, Lawrence J., Mr. (Box-folder 19: 43)
      - Powell, Joseph Lester, Mr. (Box-folder 19: 44)
      - Radon, JeniK, Mr. (Box-folder 19: 45)
      - Rainwater, Betty, Ms. (Box-folder 19: 46)
      - Rand, Sidney A., Honorable (Box-folder 19: 47)
      - Read, Ben H., Honorable (Box-folder 19: 48)
      - Reed, Arlene L. (Box-folder 19: 49)
      - Rentschler, James, Mr. (Box-folder 19: 50)
      - Reuter, William C., Prof. (Box-folder 19: 51)
      - Riccio, Robert A. (Box-folder 19: 52)
      - Ridgway, Rozanne L. (Box-folder 19: 53)
      - Robinson, Janipher W., Mr. (Box-folder 19: 54)
      - Ruth, Arne, Mr. (Box-folder 19: 55)
      - Sammons, James H., M.D. (Box-folder 19: 56)
      - Sands, Harold W., Mr. (Box-folder 19: 57)
      - Sawhill, John, Honorable (Box-folder 19: 58)
      - Scher, Evelyn (Box-folder 19: 59)
      - Schram, Marty, Mr. (Box-folder 19: 60)
      - Schultz, Theodore W. (Box-folder 19: 61)
      - Segerhammar, Kemp, Pastor and Mrs. (Box-folder 19: 62)
      - Sherwood, Robert K. (Box-folder 19: 63)
      - Sieverts, Frank A. (Box-folder 19: 64)
      - Silfverstrand, Bengt (Box-folder 19: 65)
      - Sillen, Bo, Mr. (Box-folder 19: 66)
      - Simonson, Juhan, Mr. (Box-folder 19: 67)
      - Smith, Alan M., Prof. (Box-folder 19: 68)
      - Smith, David S., Honorable (Box-folder 19: 69)
      - Solli, Olaf (Box-folder 19: 70)
      - Somerville, Ronald K., Esquire (Box-folder 19: 71)
      - Strauss, Harlan J. (Box-folder 19: 72)
      - Sullivan, Beth, Ms. (Box-folder 19: 73)
      - Svensson, Hans (Box-folder 19: 74)
      - Swanson, Sylvia, Ms. (Box-folder 19: 75)
      - Tighe, Eugene F., Jr., Lt. Gen. (Box-folder 19: 76)
      - Ulsten, Ola (Box-folder 19: 77)
      - Vance, Cyrus, Honorable (Box-folder 19: 78)
      - Vest, George S., Honorable (Box-folder 19: 79)
      - Vindeveg, Leif, Mr. (Box-folder 19: 80)
      - Vine, Richard D., Honorable (Box-folder 19: 81)
      - Vleck, John H. van, Prof. and Mrs. (Box-folder 19: 82)
      - Voll, Peter R. (travel schedule is enclosed) (Box-folder 19: 83)
      - Wachtmeister, Wilhelm, Honorable (Box-folder 19: 84)
      - Wanyoike, Joel, His Excellency, Ambassador (Box-folder 19: 85)
      - Watson, Barbara M., Honorable (Box-folder 19: 86)
      - Webster, Albert K., Mr. (Box-folder 19: 87)
      - Westerberg, Bengt, Mr. (Box-folder 19: 88)
      - Westerlund, Birgit, Mrs. (Box-folder 19: 89)
      - Wexler, Anne, Ms. (Box-folder 19: 90)
      - Widen, Albin, Dr. (Box-folder 19: 91)
      - Wikstrom, Jan-Erik, Mr. (Box-folder 19: 92)
      - Wilmink, Janet (Box-folder 19: 93)
      - Winberg, Kristina (clipping and an announcement in Swedish are enclosed) (Box-folder 19: 94)
      - Wirten, Rolf, Honorable (Box-folder 19: 95)
      - Wise, Phil, Mr. (Box-folder 19: 96)
      - Wydler, John W., Honorable (Box-folder 19: 97)
    - Memoranda
      - January (Box-folder 20: 1)
      - (handwritten notes are enclosed), February (Box-folder 20: 2)
      - (includes a letter), March (Box-folder 20: 3)
      - April (Box-folder 20: 4)